<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Workings on M.Heerens</title>
    <link>https://mheerens.github.io/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Workings on M.Heerens</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2019 10:03:10 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://mheerens.github.io/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Deploying Data Science</title>
      <link>https://mheerens.github.io/projects/deployment/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2019 10:10:29 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mheerens.github.io/projects/deployment/</guid>
      <description>Data science is fine - but how do you actually make it usable for the business user?
This small project is to give an example of a modern data science product using methods such as modularization, data gathering from external sources, continuous re-training of a machine learning model, publishing and visualizing via an API - all hosted on AWS.
The main idea is to build everything around an API, and use that API for (A) controlling/triggering main fuctions such as unpdating the database, re-training the machine learning model and&amp;hellip; (B) &amp;hellip;making data and results available through jsons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Classical Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://mheerens.github.io/projects/machine-learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2019 10:10:29 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mheerens.github.io/projects/machine-learning/</guid>
      <description>This project is two things at the same time: A workflow structure for doing machine learning (in this case: building and evaluating a model), and at the same time a collection of frequently used functions. The Goal of this project is to provide a solid template that can - after customization - be used for many of the &amp;ldquo;classical classification&amp;rdquo; and/or regression problems that might occur in a hand-on business context.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making Business Intelligent</title>
      <link>https://mheerens.github.io/projects/business-intelligence/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2019 10:10:29 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mheerens.github.io/projects/business-intelligence/</guid>
      <description>The best way for the business user to actually make a real use of data is to do classic Business Intelligence with software products like Tableau, QlikSense and SiSense.
In various projects across different industries such as e-commerce, automotive, retail and small to medium sized production companies I developed and deployed simple yet effective data models and dashboards thus giving business users a better understanding for their business.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>